My name is Praveen, and I am 40 years old
I work in IT
While working on the computer a lot, I got a lot of shoulder and neck pain
For 3-4 weeks, it became a hassle and hurt a lot
I got checked in a hospital, and they gave me painkillers. I used it for 2 weeks.
It relieved the pain, but if I didn't take the tablets, the pain started again
The doctor never told me about physical therapy, but I had hope
it'd make my condition even a little bit better
The doctor finally suggested it, and I came to NRI Seva
After a while, sir and madam told me to get an X-ray, so I went out and got an X-ray
so I could be properly analyzed
I showed them where the pain was, they analyzed the x-ray,
and started me on treatments for my neck and shoulder
They gave me a sandbag for support for my shoulder.
I couldn't even carry that one-kilo bag
I even requested saying it was very heavy. But the past 3-4 days
the bag wasn't heavy anymore because of the treatment
After almost two weeks of treatment, my current condition
is 95% better than my original condition